https://1strate.co.uk/privacy-policy/

——
Privacy Notice : Business Telephone Systems, 1st Rate Comms Ltd
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your right to privacy is very important to us. 1st Rate Comms Ltd recognise that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. We believe this information should only be used to help us provide you with a better service. That's why we have put a policy in place to protect your personal information. Below is a summary of our policy.
By submitting personal data manually or in electronic form to this web site, or by using this site, you give your consent that all personal data you submit may be processed in the manner and for the purposes described below.
What personal information do we collect? When making a purchase with 1st Rate Comms Ltd, we will collect your contact information, which includes name, address, email address and phone number, as well as payment information. When you become a 1st Rate Comms Ltd customer you automatically subscribe to electronic newsletter and special offer promotions. You can adjust your email preferences and/or unsubscribe from certain communications via your 1st Rate Comms Ltd Control Panel
Protecting your privacy We will take appropriate steps to protect your privacy. Whenever you provide sensitive information (for example, a credit card number to make a purchase), we will take all reasonable steps to protect it, such as encrypting your card number. We will also take reasonable security measures to protect your personal information in storage. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for marketing purposes. We do not store or keep any record of your credit card details once your transaction has taken place. This is why we send out reminder emails for your renewal and not automatic billing.
On occasion, we may need to provide your name and delivery address to third parties that 1st Rate Comms Ltd may use for the purposes of delivering specific services to you (e.g., customer support.). We will not provide any of your personal information details to other companies or individuals for marketing purposes without your permission.
1st Rate Comms Ltd may provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control those websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party sites.
Your Rights to Privacy (GDPR) In preventing the use or processing of your personal data, it may delay or prevent 1st Rate Comms Ltd from fulfilling our contractual obligations with you. It may also mean that we shall be unable to provide our services or process the cancellation of your 1st Rate Comms Ltd service.
Under the latest legislation of GDPR, you have the right to object to our use of your personal data, or ask us to delete, remove or stop using it if there is no need for us to keep it. This is known as your right to be forgotten. There are legal and accountancy reasons why we will need to keep your data, but please do inform us if you think we are retaining or using your personal data incorrectly. You can do this FREE of charge.
Our Privacy Notice shall be made clear to you at the point of collection of your personal data.
You can view, edit or delete your personal data through the 1st Rate Comms Ltd control panel at anytime. You can also make choices about 1st Rate Comms Ltd's collection of your data and how it is used.
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. Please contact us directly via email, telephone, or writing to make your request.
We will not contact you for marketing purposes unless you have given us your prior consent.
Updating your information (GDPR) As part of your contract with 1st Rate Comms Ltd, you must maintain the accuracy of your information and ensure all your details, including but not limited to, name, address, title, phone number, e-mail address and payment details are kept up to date at all times.
You will always have the right to access the information we hold about you. Please email your requests to support@1strate.co.uk so that we can obtain this information for you.
Use of cookies 1st Rate Comms Ltd uses cookies for various reasons, for example, cookies enable us to track information during the domain name registration and package sign-up process. These cookies do not track individual information. Cookies from 1st Rate Comms Ltd can only be read by 1st Rate Comms Ltd. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you will not be able to carry out a transaction with 1st Rate Comms Ltd.
If you do nothing other than read pages or download information while using this web site, we will capture and store information about your visit. This information will not identify you; it relates to: • the Internet domain (e.g. www.company.co.uk) and IP address from which you access the web site • the type of browser (Internet Explorer or Netscape) and operating system (Windows, UNIX) you use • the date and time of your visit • the pages you visit • the address of the web site from which you linked to us (if applicable).
We use this information to make each visit more rewarding, and to provide us with information to help improve our service. We do not know (and do not want to know) the identities of people who visit us in this way.
Data storage in the U.K. Any information that 1st Rate Comms Ltd needs to store and process will be carried out on databases located in the UK, and in full compliance of the Data Protection Act.
How can you update the personal information you have provided to us? You can help 1st Rate Comms Ltd maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying 1st Rate Comms Ltd of any changes to your address, title, phone number or e-mail address. You can do this by updating your personal details from within your 1st Rate Comms Ltd Control Panel.
The personal information we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of collection. We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time and will provide notice of these changes on the Privacy Policy pages of our web site. You should make sure you periodically review the Privacy Policy to make sure it meets your needs.
Information Disclosure Policy Personal and account information 1st Rate Comms Ltd will not otherwise disclose its customers' personal and account information unless 1st Rate Comms Ltd has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of 1st Rate Comms Ltd, 1st Rate Comms Ltd' customers, or others, or where 1st Rate Comms Ltd has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure.
Electronic communications 1st Rate Comms Ltd also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that 1st Rate Comms Ltd stores or transmits for its customers. The circumstances under which 1st Rate Comms Ltd will disclose such electronic customer communications are when:  • it is necessary in order to provide service to the customer; • it is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of 1st Rate Comms Ltd and its customers; • it is required to cooperate with dispute policies, court orders, warrants, or other legal processes that 1st Rate Comms Ltd determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable • it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by 1st Rate Comms Ltd and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.
1st Rate Comms Ltd disclaims any intention to censor, edit or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. 1st Rate Comms Ltd will, however, review, delete or block access to communications that may harm 1st Rate Comms Ltd, its customers or third parties or otherwise infringe the rights of third parties. The grounds on which 1st Rate Comms Ltd may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of 1st Rate Comms Ltd' Acceptable Use Policy
Please note: by signing up for any of our services you agree to be bound by all 1st Rate Comms Ltd terms and conditions
This is the web site of the 1st Rate Comms Ltd and stated below is the privacy policy of the site.For each visitor to our web page, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site .If you do not want to receive an e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail.From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other departments within our organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know.If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders or quotes they have requested on-line. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations. With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with, or have special relationships with, any ad server companies.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us.Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them.Consumers can access this information by emailing us. Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, unique identifiers, transaction information. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
Categories
Home
+New Products
+ - Telephone Systems
- NEC Telephone Systems
- Orchid Telephone Systems
- iQ PBX IP Phone Systems
- Panasonic Telephone Systems
- Panasonic Phone Systems (refurbished)
+ - Panasonic Phones (refurbished)
- Phones for KXT308, 616, 624 1232
- Phones for KX-TD612, 816,1232
- Panasonic Cards (refurbished)
+ - NEC Refurbished
- NEC Phone Systems (refurbished)
You have no items to compare.
